[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Approximately what percentage of the population of the country of Papua New Guinea lives in rural areas?", "correct_answer": "86%", "incorrect_answers": ["50%", "34%", "97%"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Mel Brooks birth name?", "correct_answer": "Melvin Kaminsky", "incorrect_answers": ["Melvin Brockman", "Melcohm Krakouschy", "Melcohm Brooks"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Suns magnetic field, driven by the Solar Wind, can reach distances how far out into space?", "correct_answer": "Into Interstellar space", "incorrect_answers": ["Just past the orbit of Mercury", "Just inside the orbit of Jupiter", "Between Pluto and the Oort Cloud"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This country, whose capital city is Tegucigalpa, uses the lempira as its currency.", "correct_answer": "Honduras", "incorrect_answers": ["El Salvador", "Bolivia", "Nicaragua"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which city was the Shinsengumi group founded?", "correct_answer": "Kyoto", "incorrect_answers": ["Tokyo", "Nagasaki", "Osaka"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 1998 Jude Law romantic thriller was renamed Immortality upon its DVD release.", "correct_answer": "The Wisdom of Crocodiles", "incorrect_answers": ["Shadow of the Vampire", "Nadja", "Perfect Creature"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A cats memory is about half as retentive as a dogs.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "You have another Question. Sure, I got one question for you. Its can you deal with that is taken from what film?", "correct_answer": "Meet the Parents", "incorrect_answers": ["Meet the Fockers", "Bad Boys", "Napoleon Dynamite"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "To what geographic area is the ostrich native?", "correct_answer": "Africa", "incorrect_answers": ["Asia", "South America and Africa", "Europe and Africa"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "General Slocum was the name of a person involved in the 1904 fire in New York that resulted in over 1000 deaths.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What large mammal is the national animal of India?", "correct_answer": "Bengal tiger", "incorrect_answers": ["Water Buffalo", "Indian Rhinoceros", "Indian Elephant"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Friday the 13th, when Alice and Bill went to check the generator, it was raining. What color were their raincoats?", "correct_answer": "red and yellow", "incorrect_answers": ["green and yellow", "blue and yellow", "red and green"]}]